I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Roberts Numbering Machine Co. and UE Local 1217 CIO. 2/20/48, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1069)
  Decision: Discharge, Insubordination; Union representatives and business. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits. Case is important as it reviews the applicability of the principle of stare decisis in arbitration cases.
- Merck and Co., Inc. and Employees Organization of Merck and Co. 3/11/48 [Files A&B], 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1070)
  Decision: Contract interpretation; Incentive pay and incentive systems. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Muzak Corp. and UE, Local 430, CIO. 3/3/48., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1073)
  Decision: Rates of pay. Contains personal notes and correspondence.
- Lloyd Rogers and Co. and Int'l Fed. Of Architects, Engineers, Chemists, and Technicians, CIO. 3/1/48, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1075)
  Decision: Back pay award. Contains personal notes and correspondence.
- Anaconda Wire and Cable Co. and UE, Local 404, CIO. 3/18/48, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1076)
  Decision: Work week (bargaining in good faith). Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Acme Backing Corp. and United Gas, Coke, & Chemical Workers of America, Local 121, CIO. 3/30/48, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1077)
  Decision: Seniority, Supervisors and Foremen. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Montrose Chemical Co. and United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, Local 284. 4/27/48, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1078)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper job attitude; Improper personal conduct; Insubordination. Contains personal notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- Wilcolator Co. and UE, Local 406, CIO. 4/21/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1084)
  Decision: Layoffs; Seniority. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Warner Bros. Pictures, Inc. and Int'l Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers, and Maintenance Mechanics, Local 56, AFL. 5/4/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1085)
  Decision: Rates of pay. Contains personal notes and correspondence
- North Jersey Radio, Inc. (WNJR) and Radio Broadcast Engineers, (IBEW) Local 1212, AFL. 3/24/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1086)
  Decision: Rates of pay; Equalization. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Laufer & Rothbaum, Inc. and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 5/18/49, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1087)
  Decision: 1) Discharge; absenteeism. 2) Contractual duties; crew size. Contains personal notes and correspondence.
- Greater N.Y. Photofinishers Assn. Inc. and United Photographic Employees Union, Local 415, 7/23/48 [Files A-C], 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1089)
  Decision: Contract modification re rates of pay. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits. One should note the large supply of exhibits on both sides for an in-depth look at the N.Y. photographic industry at the time
- National Union Radio Corp. and UE, Local 445, CIO. 7/7/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1090)
  Decisions: 1) Classification of jobs, assignment of new jobs. 2) Back pay awards, suspension. 3) Layoffs, super seniority. 4) Contract interpretation, Arbitrability. 5) Premium pay, overtime, shift scheduling. 6) Management rights, shift scheduling, holid
- Economy Cover and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65 7/27/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1091)
  Decision: Rates of pay; Welfare funds; Arbitrability. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Reichhold Chemicals, Inc. and United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, Local 190 7/1/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1092)
  Decision: Discharge; Ability. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- American Cyanamid Co. and UMW, Local 12426, District 50, 7/20/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1093)
  Decisions: 1) Classification of jobs, retroactive pay. 2) Classification of jobs, rates of pay. 3) Vacation pay in relation to strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages, and recall. Contains personal notes,
- Janaug Ind. And Waiters and Waitresses Union, Local 1 7/9/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1096)
  Decision: Discharge; alcoholism, drinking, intoxication, insubordination. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Fleetwood Baking Co., Inc. and BCW, Local 50 2/23/49, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1097)
  Decisions: 1) Discharge; fights and altercations. 2) Back pay award, contract interpretation; classification of jobs. Contains personal notes, and correspondence.
- Caldwell-Philadelphia Lawn Mower Co., Inc. and IAM, Lodge 757, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1099)
  [File A] 7/9/48. Decisions: 1) Layoff; Seniority; Bumping; Probationary. 2) Call-in. 3) Overtime; Premium pay. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 1/25/49. Decision: Interpretation of past arbitration
- Max Zadek, Inc. and United Optical Workers Union, Local 208. 7/13/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1100)
  Decision: Refusal to pay, Insurance Funds. Contains personal notes, and correspondence.
- R.K. Baking Corp. and IBT, Local 802. 9/1/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1102)
  Decision: Classification of jobs. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Childs Co. and Chain Service Restaurant Employees Union, Local 42 CIO. 7/16/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1103)
  Decisions: 1) Discharge; Alcoholism, drinking, and intoxication. 2) Definitions, classification of jobs. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits. Includes a lengthy discussion of the difference between full-time employ
- National Union Radio Corp. and UE, Local 445, CIO., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1105)
  [File A] 8/10/48. Decision: Definition, Lockout. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits. [File B] 3/10/49. Decisions: 1) Incentive systems and incentive pay. 2) Rates of pay. 3) Time studies. 4) Rates of pay (new jobs vs. past practice).
- Bernacchia Bros. Inc. and TWU, Local 100. 9/2/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1106)
  Decision: Contract negotiations. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Edward E. Robinson, Inc. and Playthings, Jewelry and Novelty Union, United Industrial Union, Local 307. 9/13/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1107)
  Decision: Discharge; Incompetency and inefficiency. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits. This case has a good amount of information on specific companies' incentive systems and has various charts and graphs on employee performance which
- Nehemiah Gitelson & Sons and Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, CIO. 9/8/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1108)
  Decisions: 1) Call-in. 2) Discharge, employees rights, seniority, temporary employees. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Celluplastics Corp. and United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, Local 264, CIO. 9/16/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1109)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Callite Tungsten Corp. & UE, Local 448 CIO. 10/18/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1110)
  Decision: Vacancies. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, exhibits.
- Aluminum Co. of America and Int'l Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 702. 11/1/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1111)
  Decision: Suspension; Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; Union representatives and business. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- NY & Richmond Gas Co. and IBEW, Local 3, AFL 12/4/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1112)
  Decisions: 1) Rates of pay. 2) Welfare funds, medical insurance, pension plans. 3) Union security. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits.
- Advance Pressure Castings Co. and Int'l Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 701. 10/20/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1113)
  Decision: Discharge; Incompetency and inefficiency. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Oppenheim Collins & Co. and RWDSU, Local 1250, CIO. 10/8/48, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1114)
- Celanese Corp. of America and TWUA, Local 1874, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 1116)
  [File A] 1/23/48. Decisions: 1) Incentive pay and incentive systems. 2) Employee rights; Transfers; Assignments of new jobs. Contains personal notes, correspondence, collective agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 1/26/50. Decision: Incentive pay and inc
- Eagle Electric Manufacturing Co., Inc. and U.E., Local 475, 11/3/48, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1119)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper job attitude, improper personal conduct, dishonesty. Contains notes and correspondence.
- American Agricultural Chemical Co. and United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 246, CIO 11/1/48, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1120)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Yardley of London, Inc. and United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, Local 302, CIO 11/2/48, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1122)
  Decision: Transfer and related rates of pay. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Mack Mfg. Corp. and UAW, Local 285 11/23/48, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1123)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper personal conduct; Plant rules. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Celanese Corp. of America and TWUA, Local 1874, CIO 1/4/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1124)
  Decision: Back pay award; Suspension; Rules; Assembly line speed; Bargaining in good faith. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- H. Boker & Co., Inc. and UMW, District 50, Local 13325, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 1126)
  [File A] 12/16/48. Decision: Seniority; Bumping. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 4/14/49. Decision: Authority of arbitrator; Rates of pay; Fringe benefits. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Volco Brass & Copper Co. and Int'l Union of Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers, Local 673 12/24/48, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 1127)
  Decision: Rates of pay; Premium pay; Contract modification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Celanese Corp. of America and TWUA, Local 1874 3/16/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1130)
  Decision: Equipment and physical facilities; Improper job attitude. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Gottfried Baking Corp. and BCW, Local 150 AFL 3/4/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1131)
  Decisions: 1) Call-in pay; Reporting pay. 2) Rates of pay. 3) Discharge; Medical release. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Union New Co. and News Distribution Employees Union, Local 906 2/21/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1132)
  Decision: discharge; Improper personal conduct in regard to overtime and premium pay; Insubordination. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Taller and Cooper, Inc. and UE, Local 475, CIO 3/31/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1133)
  Decision: Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Allied Maintenance Co. and TWU 3/8/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1134)
  Decision: Discharge; Alcoholism, drinking & intoxication; Fights & altercations. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Otis Elevator Co. and Metropolitan Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists & Technicians CIO. 3/30/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1136)
  Decisions: 1) Arbitrability. 2) Files; Salary Schedules; Merit increases & merit review. 3) Fringe benefits. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Bright Star Battery Co. and IBT, Local 867, AFL. 3/25/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1138)
  Decision: Holidays and holiday pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Josephson Mfg. Co. and Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65 5/24/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1141)
  Decision: Rates of pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Bloomingdale's and RWDSU, Local 3, CIO 5/31/49 [Files A&B], 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1142)
  Decision: Layoffs; Departmental vs. enterprise seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- International Projector Corp. and UE, Local 475, CIO 7/5/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1143)
  Decision: Holidays; Lockout; Workweek. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- R.M. Hollingshead Corp. and Automotive Chemical Products Union, 22130, AFL 5/13/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1144)
  Decision: Seniority; Layoffs. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- 987 Corp. as the Manager of the Empire Theatre and Assn. of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers 6/20/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1145)
  Decision: Discharge; Improper personal conduct; Improper job attitude. Contains personal notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- General Electric Company and UE, CIO 7/13/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1146)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination; Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Graphic Arts Employing Machinists Assn., Inc. and IAM, Dist. 15, Lodge 434 6/8/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1147)
  Decisions: 1) Holidays and holiday pay. 2) Retroactive pay; Overtime. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Color Film Co. of America, Inc. and Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians, Local 702, IATSE 7/11/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1150)
  Decision: Vacations and vacation pay; Discharge. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- American Package Co. and Paper Box Makers Union, Local 299 8/17/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1151)
  Decisions: 1) Salary schedules, classification of jobs. 2) Management rights (cutting hours of full-time employee). Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- National Union Radio Corp. and UE, Local 445 7/22/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1152)
  Decision: Incentive pay and incentive systems; Time studies. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Celanese Corp. of America and TWUA, Local 1874 8/1/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1153)
  Decisions: 1) Premium pay; Workweek. 2) Suspension; Overtime; Working conditions. Contains notes, correspondence, exhibits.
- Nu-Site Optical Mfg. Corp. and United Optical Workers Union, Local 208, CIO 7/25/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1157)
  Decision: Discharge; Incompetence & inefficiency. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Union News Co. and Luncheonette and Soda Fountain Workers Union, Local 539, AFL. 8/10/49, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1162)
  Decisions: 1) Compensation (commissions) 2) Automation. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Manhattan News Co., Inc. and NMD, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1166)
  [File A] 8/5/49. Decisions: 1) Jurisdiction; Management's rights. 2) Discharge; Improper possession of company property; rules. 3) Discharge; theft. Contains notes and correspondence. [File B] 10/21/49. Decisions: 1) Back pay award; Strikes, slowdowns,
- World Telegram and NMD, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1168)
  [File A] 9/15/49. Decision: Layoff; Assignment of new jobs; Insubordination. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements. [File B] 10/225/49. Decision: Premium pay; Overtime. Contains notes and correspondence. [File C] 12/5/49. Decision: Classifi
- Post Home News and NMD 9/28/49, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1169)
  Decision: Removal of work from bargaining unit; Management rights. Contains notes and correspondence.
- National Sugar Refining Co. and United Sugar Refinery Workers. Local 580, CIO. 12/28/49 [Files A&B], 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1173)
  Decisions: 1) Equalization. 2) Schedules of work; work week. 3) Seniority; Assignment of jobs. 4) Contracting out. 5) Premium pay; Schedules of work; Work week. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. This is a good discussion of arbitration in rela
- Sun and NMD. 12/5/49, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1175)
  Decision: Vacation pay; Fringe benefits, and management rights. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Passaic County News Co. and NMD. 12/6/49, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1177)
  Decisions: 1) Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; Supervisors and foremen; Union representatives and business. 2) Posting. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Weinberg News Co. and NMD. 1/12/49, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1178)
  Decision: Discharge; Negligence and carelessness (in driving). Contains notes and correspondence.
- Daily News and NMD. 1/9/50 (Box 5, Folder 1180)
  Decision: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; Damages. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- K & T Distributors, Inc. and NMD. 3/17/50, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1191)
  Decision: Discharge; Interpretation of past arbitration award; Back pay award. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Mack Mfg. Corp. and UAW, Local 824, CIO. 7/6/50, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1193)
  Decisions: 1) Classification of jobs; Supervisors and foremen; Seniority. 2) Incentive pay and incentive systems. 3) Assignment of New Jobs; Rates of pay. 4&5) Time studies. 6) Classification of jobs. 7) Refusal to pay. 8) Layoffs; Bumping. 9) Posting
- Metropolitan News Co. and NMD. 12/7/50, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1227)
  Decision: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- E.R. Squibb & Sons and United Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers of America, Local 138, CIO. 1/3/51., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1229)
  Decision: Arbitrability; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Newark News dealers Supply Co., Inc. and NMD, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1230)
  [File A] 11/2/50. Decisions: 1) Equalization (for non-union employees). 2) Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 12/1/50. Decision: Interpretation of previous arbitration award; retroa
- John Waldron Corp. and IAM, Dist. 47. 12/1/50, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1231)
  Decision: Seniority; Reinstatement. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- National Union Radio Corp. and UE, CIO. 3/8/50, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1233)
  Decision: Discharge; Incompetence and inefficiency. Contains notes and correspondence.
- Herald Tribune and NMD. 8/21/50, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1235)
  Decisions: 1) Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; Assignment of new jobs; Removal of work from the bargaining unit. 2) Interpretation of past arbitration award. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Borden's Farm Products Co. and IBT, Local 602, AFL. 4/25/51 [Files A&B], 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1236)
  Decision: Overtime; Refusal to pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Interborough News Co. and News Distribution Employees Union, Local 906. 12/28/50, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1240)
  Decision: Vacation pay in relation to termination of business. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- 35 Hamilton Place, Inc. and BSEIU, Local 219. 2/2/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1248)
  Decision: Contract modification; Rates of pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- American Cyanamid Co. and Int'l Chemical Workers Union, Local 143, AFL. 3/23/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1250)
  Decision: Promotion; Ability; Seniority. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Kidde Manufacturing Co. and UE, Local 437. 5/11/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1251)
  Decision: Discharge; Recall. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- Celanese Corp. of America and TWUA, Local 1874 CIO., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1253)
  [File A] 10/22/51. Decision: Rates of pay; Assignment of new jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 10/22/51. Decision: Suspension; Incompetence and inefficiency. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. [File
- News Syndicate Co. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y. 4/26/51., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1254)
  Decision: Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- New York Herald Tribune and Newspaper Guild of N.Y., Local 3, 5/31/57 [Files A&B], 1957 (Box 6, Folder 1259)
  Decision: Discharge; improper personal conduct; Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication (off work); Absences. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. This case is important as it recognizes that when a message is sent to an employee on his
- N.Y. Post Corp. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y. 7/20/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1260)
  Decision: Reinstatement; Assignment of new jobs; Contracting out. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- WPIX, Inc. and Radio and Television Broadcast Engineers Union, IBEW, Local 1212, AFL. 8/20/51 [Files A&B], 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1263)
  Decision: Salary schedules; Interpretation of past arbitration award. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Wilcolator Co. and UE, Local 406. 9/12/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1266)
  Decision: Discharge; Absences; Improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Continental Can Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 1269)
  [File A] 9/10/51. Decisions: 1) Super seniority, Union officials and business; Layoffs. 2) Removal of work from bargaining unit. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 2/15/52. Decisions: 1) Vacation pay. 2) Schedules of wor
- G.F. Richter Mfg. Co. and UE, Local 1227, CIO. 9/13/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1271)
  Decisions: 1) Retroactive pay; Refusal to pay. 2) Withdrawal of existing benefits. Contains notes, correspondence, and agreements.
- Remington Arms Co., Inc. and Industrial Machine & Office Workers Union. 12/14/51 [Files A&B], 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1273)
  Decisions: 1) Equalization. 2) Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Old Roumanian Restaurant and Chefs, Cooks & Pastry Cooks, Local 89. 10/26/51, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1274)
  Decision: Discharge; Insubordination; Improper job attitude; Improper personal conduct. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- New York Telephone Co. and Empire State Telephone Union 12/27/51, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 1276)
  Decision: Discharge; Management rights; Rules; Dishonesty. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- Newark Baking Companies and IAM, District 47 2/27/52 [Files A&B], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1277)
  Decision: Layoffs; Notice. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Deluxe Laboratories, Inc. and Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians, Local 702, IATSE 11/5/51, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 1278)
  Decisions: Contract modification; Schedules of work. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- American Machine and Foundry Co. and UAW, Local 116, CIO 1/11/52, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1280)
  Decision: Contract modification; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits.
- News Syndicate Co., Inc. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y., 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 1281)
  [File A] 11/29/51. Decisions: 1) Part-time employees; Employees rights. 2) Interpretation of past arbitration award. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, and exhibits. [File B] 3/17/52. Decision: Rates of pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agr
- Brunswick Ordnance Corp. and UAW, Local 824. 3/18/52 [Files A&B], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1283)
  Decisions: 1) Classification of jobs; Rates of pay. 2,3,4,5) Posting; Classification of jobs. 6) Overtime; Absences. 7) Overtime; past practice. 8) Overtime; Transfers. 9) Damages; Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes, correspondence,
- The Associated Press and the American Newspaper Guild. 1/17/52 [Files A-C], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1284)
  Decision: Rates of pay. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements, exhibits, and interim and adjustment awards (1/11/52 & 3/5/52). Many important and interesting exhibits are present in this case which demonstrate the enormous amount of research whic
- Warner-Hudnut, Inc. and United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, Local 585, CIO. 10/14/52, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1309)
  Decision: Assignment of jobs; Classification of jobs. Contains notes, correspondence, agreements and exhibits.
- Duplan Corp. and TWUA. 10/1/52 [Files A-D], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1310)